growershouse.com 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy for GrowersHouse.com

## Privacy Policy

**We will never, ever, under any circumstances share any information we collect about our customers and their transactions with anyone, period.** We hate spam as much as you do. For maximum security, we do not allow our system to store credit card information. Also, we ship every package discretely unless it is clearly expressed that discrete shipping is not necessary. 

## How We Protect Your Data:

Whether you are shopping online or in our store, we use security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us. **Growers House** uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL protects information you submit via our Web site such as ordering information including your name, address and credit card number. 

## Information We Collect: 

Like many other websites, we also collect information through cookies and other automated means. Cookies are commonly used by websites to save data on your computer. The information we collect from cookies may include your IP address, browser and device characteristics, referring URLs, and a record of your interactions with our websites. We use cookies to create a more personalized shopping experience on our website. In combination with other information we collect, this cookie may facilitate the tailoring of unique personalized offers based on your preferences. To help us understand and enhance our interactions with visitors to our websites, we collect data using Google web analytics. 

Please let us know if there's anything we can do to make your shopping experience more enjoyable. Remember, our house is your home, and we want you to feel comfortable with us. 

This privacy policy sets out how Growers House uses and protects any information that you give Growers House when you use this website. Growers House is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Growers House may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

## What We Collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What We Do With The Information We Gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## How We Use Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

## Links To Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

## Controlling Your Personal Information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Growers House 3635 E 34TH ST TUCSON, AZ 85713 . 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

GrowersHouse.com uses Google AdWords for Conversion Tracking. No personal information is ever shared with Google, only that a purchase was made. 

**International Shipping Powered by**

We have partnered with Bongo International to service our international customers.

Checkout by clicking the “Outside the U.S.?” button or at checkout, choose your international destination from the country drop down menu. Once you click the button or select your country and attempt to checkout, you will be automatically transferred to [Bongo's Secure International Checkout](http://www.bongous.com/) page where you will be provided with international shipping costs as well as duties and taxes for your shipment.

Upon completion of your order, Bongo will charge your credit card for the entire purchase. We will ship the goods to Bongo's Global Distribution Facility where Bongo will process the order and transport the goods to your international address. There are no additional fees or registration processes with this service.
